question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock's film Psycho, it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The film 2001: A Space Odyssey was released on December 31st, 2000.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in The Aviator.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Minions was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The word Inception came from the 2010 blockbuster hit Inception.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The movie The Nightmare before Christmas was all done with physical objects.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "In the original script of The Matrix, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Han Soloco-pilot and best friend, Chewbacca, is an Ewok.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]
